Tequana S. Napper

852 Potomac Lancaster, Texas 75134 (972) 218-8917 / (972) 900-1812

Tequana_napper@yahoo.com

Personal Statement

I am a smart individual, king, and always willing to offer a helping hand. I am always up for learning new things and i am willing to go the distance for whomever i gain employment with. I have very little experience in the working field but i am ready and available to start conquer.

Objective

Seeking entry level position in a growing company

• Education

Lancaster High School August 2008- June 2011

Graduated HS Diploma Received

Cedar Valley College January 2012- present

Degree in Progress Medical Field

• Experience

Karen's 24 Hour childcare & Daycare June 2010- August 2010

Daycare Summer Help Karen Lee, 972- 218-

8294

Duties Included: Cleaning, preparing snacks for children, reading to children, interacting with the children.

O'Reilly Auto Parts District Center

May 2012- October 2012

Duties Included: Keeping my work area clean at all times pulling orders for the customers to be shipped to the stores.

• Six Flags Over Texas

January 2015- August 2015

Duties Included: Having good customer service to the guest at the park ask the walk into the park and keeping my work area clean at all time during park hours.

(800) 463-3339

Duties Included: Unloading trucks at a fast past until the job was done and keeping my work area clean at all times.

Wis International

Aug 2015- Feb 2017

Duties Included: Doing inventory counting the stores merchandise such ask family dollar, dollar tree, kohls and more.

(817) 640-8900

• Volunteer Experience

City of Lancaster

April 2012

Helping with Tornado Clean up and Donations for the City of Lancaster

New Lancaster Community Church

April 2011

Helping to clean the church by vacuuming, dusting, mopping, and taking out trash disposal.

• Hobbies

My hobbies include: Searching the web, swimming, reading, shopping and communication with friends and family.